# 1117, 20 Edgecliff Golfway, North York, M3C 3A4.

- +1647-287-0437
- ashishkotadia03@gmail.com 

  ✓

# Ashish Kotadia

Strong interpersonal and computation skills and well equipped to manage administrative tasks. Currently working in the financial environment as a Financial service representative and previously experienced in the Customer service background. Always willing to go an extra mile for the company and thrive to achieve the goals. Excited and motivated to work for the organization with full integrity and zest.

#### **Skills**

- Excellent communicational skills to interact positively with customers and provide effective response.
- Experience working in a team environment and handling a team as well.
- Enthusiastic and Excellent persuasive skills
- Strong organizational, analytical, and problem-solving abilities
- Expertized in using MS Office.
- Proven ability to multitask and delivery the desired results.

# **Experience**

**DECEMBER 2021 - FEBRUARY 2024** 

# **Financial service Representative. (CIBC)**

- Meeting and exceeding productivity targets by handling every interaction with topnotch customer service.
- Working with clients to develop financial planning strategies and solutions through evaluation of finances
- Conducts research to answer questions and handle issues using multiple systems and resources
- Addressing customer complaints and queries and try to resolve them efficiently in a timely manner.
- Upholding strict quality control policies and procedures during customer interaction.

#### FEBRUARY 2020 - OCTOBER 2021

### **Financial Service representative. (Gatestone)**

- Processed payment transactions over the phone by following the rules and guidelines of the FDCPA.
- Negotiating, planning, and assisting customers with correct payment options and provide the best plan that suits the customers in the long run.
- Managed high volume of calls and provided effective response to the customers and focused on de-escalating issue to the higher authority.
- Interviewed customers regarding the reason of delinquency and avoided further delinquency on the accounts.
- Provided timely, efficient, and courteous response to customers.

#### **MAY 2017 - JANUARY 2020**

### **Customer service representative.** (Subway Restaurant).

- Delivered exceptional customer service by ensuring that customers loyalty is built.
- Handled a team of employees and oversaw the inventory and day-to-day business operations.
- Increased the customer base by 10 %.
- Ensured store is visually appealing to company standards, through proper product presentation.
- Performed cash register duties on every shifts.

### **Education**

**SEPTEMBER 2016 – APRIL 2019** 

# Advance Diploma in Business Administration- International Business / Seneca College of Applied Arts and Technology

- Gained knowledge regarding SAP software.
- Acquired leadership skills through various group projects at Seneca.
- Gained knowledge regarding day-to day business operations.
- Learned basic Accounting and Finance.
- Learned how to use advance Excel Functions.

# **Achievements at Seneca College**

• Shark's Pond finalist (An Entrepreneurial project at Seneca college)

# **Volunteer Experience**

#### **JANUARY 2012 – AUGUST 2015**

 Aga Khan Scouting and Guiding Troop leader for group of Scouts.

#### **MARCH 2013 - MARCH 2015**

Aga Khan Youth and Sports Board
 Member of Aga Khan Youth and Sports Board.

#### **MARCH 2013 - MARCH 2014**

 Aga Khan Education Service Co-convener of Education Board.